https://www.colts.com/footer/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Advertising
Indianapolis Colts Website Privacy Policy
Last Updated on 5/1/2020
This Website Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") applies to the Indianapolis Colts, Inc.'s websites, www.colts.com, forums.colts.com and www.coltsroundup.com (collectively, "Websites"), and the mobile applications that link to or post this Privacy Policy (collectively, "Services"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information the Colts may collect, how the Colts may collect it, with whom the Colts may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding the Colts' collection of information and the Colts' use and disclosure to other parties of information the Colts may have collected from you. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that is collected or obtained through sites or services that do not link to this Privacy Policy (including the Team Pro Shop) or information collected by the National Football League ("NFL") or the other NFL Member Clubs.
If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that the Colts have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact the Colts' U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personally identifiable information" or "personal information," the Colts mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as a favorite team or player, is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.
Please read the information below to learn more about the Colts' data collection policies and practices.
Types Of Information That May Be Collected
How Information May Be Collected
How We Use The Information Collected
With Whom The Information May Be Shared
Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards
Links To Other Websites
Security
A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy
Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy
Correcting/Updating Personal Information
Your California Privacy Rights
Questions About This Privacy Policy
Ways To Contact Us About Your Privacy Rights
1. Types Of Information That May Be Collected
The following are the types of information the Colts may collect:
Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the Websites, the Colts may ask you to provide certain information when you register with our Services, sign up for contests or sweepstakes, use a send-to-a-friend feature, participate in surveys, access various content or features, submit comments or content, or directly contact us with questions or feedback including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, unique identifiers such as your user name, demographic information such as your gender, and financial information, such as your credit card number or similar information; precise geo-location information; communication preferences; search queries; comments and other information posted in our interactive online forums; correspondence and other information that you send to us; additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent; information about your contacts such as name and e-mail address. "Personal information" means information that can identify a specific individual, such as your name, gender, address, phone number, e-mail address, or other contact information, whether at work or at home. Other information that we may collect, includes gender, age, first name, username and password. Data collected from parents regarding children (under the age of 13) would only be the children's name, and would be for usage of event attendance.
The Colts collect an e-mail address from each user in the registration process which protects the Websites from spam "bots" that search out and attack unprotected registrations. Our registration process immediately rejects anyone under the age of 13 years old. In the case where a user contacts us via the "Contact Us" area of the Websites, we will respond to this one-time email and delete any email address that is associated with a user under the age of 13.
Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Websites, such as your landing page, order of pages viewed, and other click stream data. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data" section below.
When you download and use our Services, we automatically collect information on the type of device you use, operating system version, and the device identifier (or "UDID").
The Colts collect your location-based information for the purpose of identifying a nearby place for which you may be searching and for Geofencing purposes within Lucas Oil Stadium. We will only share this information with our mapping provider for the sole purpose of providing you the service.
Mobile Analytics: The Colts use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile Software on your phone. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that occur within the application, aggregated usage, performance data, and where the application was downloaded from. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personally identifiable information you submit within mobile applications.
Email Communications: When you open emails from the Colts, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you, what emails you send us, and what emails you may be receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates, together with personal information contained in the emails. Additionally, we keep a record of what communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.
Information from Other Sources: The Colts may receive information about you from other sources and add it to the personal information we have collected. For example, we receive magazine subscription lists from the NFL. Data may also be collected from tools such as Formstack, ExactTarget, DonationXchange, or social media platforms.
2. How Information May Be Collected
We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Websites and via Mobile Applications, including but not limited to those described below:
Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Websites may choose to offer, such as newsletters or contests. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Websites. Samples of information collected on the Websites would include, but not limited to, name, email address, age, mailing address, zip code, hobbies, special skills, GPA, ticket history, season ticket member status, marital status, gender, household income, and favorite player. If you are completing a registration form for your child/children under 13 years of age, only the first name(s) of the child/children will be collected and stored. You should specifically grant permission for us to post a photo, artwork, video, or essay you submit on behalf of your child. Likewise, you should specifically grant permission to enter your child in any contest, sweepstakes, or promotion.
Newsletters, Emails and Push Notifications: We offer free newsletters and push notifications to share information with you about the Website, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Websites. You may also choose to receive push notifications from us. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may opt out of receiving commercial emails from the Colts by clicking on the opt-out or "unsubscribe" link included in the commercial e-mails you receive. You may opt out of receiving push notifications by turning off push notifications at the device level. Please note that opt-out requests may take some time to be effective. Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that you request or that are not commercial in nature. For example, we may contact you concerning any purchases you have made with the Colts, even if you opt out of receiving unsolicited commercial email messages. You may also contact us at webmaster@colts.com.
Contests or Sweepstakes: The Colts periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Websites that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Websites. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the Websites, such as on a winner's page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Websites, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we do not collect your information, and we have no control over the information collected from you. Accordingly, we urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.
Participation in these promotions, contests and sweepstakes is completely voluntary. The requested information typically includes contact information, such as name, shipping address, e-mail address, and telephone number. If the parent does not provide permission to use the personal information of their child/children, the child/children will not be able to participate in the promotion, contest or sweepstakes. We will use the personal information provided to us only to notify winners and award prizes.
Surveys or Voting: From time-to-time, we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Websites.
Social Networking Services: We have worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through our Services. For example, you can use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Facebook, Google+, and others to share information about your experience on our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services. These social networking services may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including information about your contacts on those social networking services.
You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Facebook, Google+, Yahoo!) to an account through our Services. This may allow you to use your credentials from the other sites or services to sign in to certain features on our Services. If you link your account from a third-party site or service, we may collect information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be governed by this Privacy Policy.
Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on the Colts' Websites. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie-enabled Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
Blog / Forum Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at webmaster@colts.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
Cookies: As with many Websites, our Websites uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a unique, random number that is stored in the browser on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify you, just the computer that is used to visit the site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit our website and where visitors go on the site. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the website. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Websites, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Websites are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Websites. Cookies may also allow the Websites to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookies data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.
The Colts do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information collected to determine your identity, your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information.
Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)
Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our Websites by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not combine information collected through clear gifs with other personal information collected to determine your identity, your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information.
IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our Websites (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP, your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We do not currently combine this information with personally identifiable information but if that changes in the future, we will revise this Privacy Policy. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Websites. Click- stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Websites, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.
We use local storage objects (LSOs) such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences.
Third Parties, with whom the Colts partner to provide certain features on our Websites, or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity, use LSOs to collect and store information.
Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html.
Transaction Information: If you conduct a financial transaction with our Websites, such as buy season tickets or official Colts' merchandise, we will ask you to complete an order form that will request certain information from you, including contact information, demographic information and financial information. We will use this information to complete the transaction that you have requested, i.e., to deliver the information, products or other services that you order, and to invoice you. For your protection, such information is collected and stored through encrypted means.
3. How We Use The Information Collected
As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:
Contact you about the Websites
Contact you relating to your membership status as we use membership areas in the Websites
Confirm or fulfill an order you have made
Inform you of a prize you have won; monitor or improve the use of the Websites
Customize the advertising and content you see
Publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features
Monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Websites
Maintain website security
Enhance navigation
Send you push notifications from time-to-time in order to update you about any events or promotions that we may be running
Send you our newsletter
Send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.
When you provide us with personal information about your contacts we will only use this information for the specific reason for which it is provided.
If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request that it be removed from our database, please contact us at webmaster@colts.com.
4. With Whom The Information May Be Shared
At times, we may share your personal information with others for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which your personal information may be shared with others and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your personal information shared. Below are ways in which we do share your personal information:
Compliance with Legal Authorities
In certain situations, the Colts may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including but not limited to, meeting the requirements of national security or law enforcement agencies.
We may also disclose your personal information, as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
Agents: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, sending e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, Website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes (like sending you marketing offers about their products). Those businesses include, but are not limited to: eSports Partners, www.indianapoliscoltsproshop.com, MBNA America Bank NA., www.nflextrapoints.com, www.applyonlinenow.com, DonationXchange, and others. You are submitting your personal information directly to some of these agents even though the pages have the look and the feel of the Colts' Websites, and their privacy policy may apply. For example, embedded forms for occasional sponsored content/promotions, proshop pages, nflextrapoints pages, all connect directly with our agents. In addition, several NFL services, including Fantasy, Game Pass, and rewind, are handled directly by the NFL and framed into our Websites.
Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information
Opt-In / Opt-Out Offers: When you provide us with personal information, you may be presented with the opportunity to share your personal information with third parties for various purposes, such as receiving information or special offers. An opt-in/opt-out message will ask you if you would like your personal information to be shared. When you allow us to share your personal information with third parties, we require third parties who have access to that personal information to agree to abide by our current Privacy Policy. Once the information is transferred, however, we cannot control the privacy practices of these other third-parties.
Third-Party Offers: Throughout the Websites, you may be presented with opportunities to receive special offers from third parties. By participating in these offers, you consent to allowing your personal information to be shared with third parties. When you allow us to share your personal information with third parties, we require third parties who have access to that personal information to agree to abide by our current Privacy Policy. We cannot control the privacy practices of these other third parties. You should review the privacy practices of such third parties prior to providing your personally identifiable information.
Other Promotional Offers: We may send offers to you on behalf of our marketing partners. When we do this, we do not give that partner your name and address. If you do not want to receive such offers, you may reply to "Unsubscribe," change your Preference Profile page, or through other procedures we notify you about on our Websites.
Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: The Websites may use a third party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Websites or may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on the Websites. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to our Websites and other websites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or websites you might be interested in. Audience and Traffic Measurement Services allow us to collect anonymous traffic and behavior information from our Websites by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. Our third party partners may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on the Websites and other websites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.
Business Transfers: In the event that all, or substantially all, of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally Identifiable Information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer.
See "Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy And Notification Of Changes To The Policy" section below.
Administrative or Legal Process: Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights, or protect the rights of other users of the Colts' Websites.
5. Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards
The Websites may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any personal information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.
6. Links To Other Websites
You should be aware that when you are on the Colts' Websites, you could be directed to other websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off one of our Websites and onto a different website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use their website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a website that is linked to one of our Websites, you should consult that website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.
7. Security
Our Websites incorporate reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your personal information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at webmaster@colts.com.
We may retain your personal information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
8. A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy
The Websites are general audience websites.If we have actual knowledge that a user is under the age of 13 years old, we will delete any personally identifiable information collected from the child as soon as possible. If we collect a child's personally identifiable information from the child's parent or guardian, we will do so in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (15 U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) including, without limitation, obtaining necessary parental consent. For more information about the privacy practices of an affiliated children's website, such as NFLPlayFootball.com, please consult the privacy policy at the children's website.
The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web Website (www.the-dma.org) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website (www.getnetwise.org) to learn more about parental control tools.
9. Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy And Notification Of Changes To The Policy
By using our Websites, you signify your agreement to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our Websites and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your personal information to be used under the terms of the new Privacy Policy, if you do not respond to our email within 30 days or continue to use the Websites 30 days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.
10. Correcting/Updating/Deleting Personal Information
Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. In addition, If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may request that we update or remove certain personal information by signing into your account and making the required changes, by emailing webmaster@colts.com, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request within 30 days.
You may opt-out of location based services in the mobile applications at any time by editing the setting at the device level or by emailing us at webmaster@colts.com.
If you no longer wish to receive push notifications, you may turn them off at the device level. To ensure you receive proper notifications, we will need to collect certain information about your device such as operating system and user identification information.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
11. Your California Privacy Rights
A California privacy law that went into effect on January 1, 2005, allows California residents to obtain specific information about a business's privacy practices if it shares information with other companies for those companies' direct marketing purposes.
As explained in this Privacy Policy, whenever you agree to let us collect personal information about you, we will always provide you with an option to prevent this personal information from being shared for non-administrative purposes with third parties. You can exercise this option at any time by following the steps outlined above.
Some web browsers may transmit "do-not-track" signals to the websites with which the user communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.
Because the Websites have a comprehensive Privacy Policy and provide you with details on how you may opt-in / opt-out of the use of your personal information by third parties for direct marketing purposes, we are not required to provide you with this information.
If you are a California resident and have questions about our compliance with this law, please send an email to webmaster@colts.com.
Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: We may use third-parties to serve advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web technologies to collect information about users' online activities over time and across different websites. To manage your preferences you may opt out here http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/. The Services may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow users to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. Nielsen believes that you should have a choice about whether to contribute to our research and insights. To opt out of Nielsen measurement, you need only to activate the "Limit Ad Tracking" (for iOS devices) or "Opt out of Ads Personalization" (for Android devices) option in your devices settings. For web, please visit: http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy to learn more about the Nielsen digital measurement products and your choices in regard to them.
12. Questions About This Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of our Websites, please contact webmaster@colts.com.
Questions may also be directed to:
Indianapolis Colts, Inc.
Attn: Website Privacy Policy
7001 West 56th Street
Indianapolis, IN 46254
13. Ways To Contact Us About Your Privacy Rights
On The Web: Web Form
*Call Us: *1-866-I-OPT-OUT, service code 861
Email Us: webmaster@colts.com
Advertising
InstagramTwitterFacebookSnapchatShop IconProfile Overlay
AvatarAddAirplayArrow LeftArrow RightArrow UpArrow DownAudioBack 5sBack 10sBack 30sCalendarChartCheckDownLeftRightUpChromecast OffChromecast OnCloseClosed CaptionsBench OffBench OnBroad OffBroad OnVertical OffVertical OnCommentDockDoneDownloadDraftFantasyFilterForward 5sForward 10sForward 30sFull Screen OffFull Screen OnGamepassGamesInsightsKeyLeaveLiveCombineDraftFantasyMenu GamesMenu NetworkMenu NewsMenu PlayoffsMenu Pro BowlMenu ShopMenu StandingsMenu StatsMenu Super BowlMenu TeamsMenu TicketsMenuMore HorizontalMore VerticalMy LocationNetworkNewsPauseplayMultiple PlayersSingle PlayerPlaylistPlayoffsPro BowlPurgeRefreshRemoveReplaySearchSettingsShare AndroidShare Copy URLShare EmailShare FacebookShare InstagramShare iOSShare SnapchatShare TwitterSkip NextSkip PreviousStandingsStarStatsSwapTeamsTicketsVideoVisibility OffVisibility OnVolume HiVolume LowVolume MediumVolume MuteWarningWebsite
Caret downCaret upAt
The browser you are using is no longer supported on this site. It is highly recommended that you use the latest versions of a supported browser in order to receive an optimal viewing experience. The following browsers are supported: Chrome, Edge (v80 and later), Firefox and Safari.
Got it!
